Mystic River Watershed Association Records MS055
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- General subject files, 1924 -- 1993; 1967 -- 1990; MS055.003; 23.65 Linear Feet
  - Industriplex, 1970 -- 1977; MS055.003.024.00015 (Box 24)
  - Fresh Pond Reservation master plan, 1978; MS055.003.024.00016 (Box 24)
  - Woburn, 1970 -- 1989; MS055.003.024.00017 (Box 24)
  - Everett Power Project final environmental impact report, 1988; MS055.003.024.00018 (Box 24)
  - Everett Power Project final environmental impact report, 1988; MS055.003.024.00019 (Box 24)
  - Everett Power Project final environmental impact report, 1988; MS055.003.024.00020 (Box 24)
  - Woburn environmental studies, phase 1 report, volume 1: environmental assessment, 1983; MS055.003.024.00021 (Box 24)
  - Woburn environmental studies, phase 1 report, volume 1: environmental assessment, 1983; MS055.003.024.00022 (Box 24)
  - Woburn environmental studies, phase 1 report, volume 2: appendices/data procedures, 1983; MS055.003.024.00023 (Box 24)
  - Woburn environmental studies, phase 1 report, volume 2: appendices/data procedures, 1983; MS055.003.024.00024 (Box 24)
  - Woburn environmental studies, phase 1 report, volume 3: subsurface data/maps/figures, 1983; MS055.003.024.00025 (Box 24)
  - Water, MS055.003.024.00026 (Box 24)
  - Environmental impact statement, roadway improvements in the Alewife corridor, 1977; MS055.003.024.00027 (Box 24)
  - Traffic summary: Alewife area, 1977; MS055.003.024.00028 (Box 24)
  - Recommendation for traffic improvements in the Alewife/North Cambridge area, 1977; MS055.003.024.00029 (Box 24)
  - Draft summary history of land use and transportation development and recent planning in the Alewife area, 1981; MS055.003.024.00030 (Box 24)
  - Environmental notification form: Craddock Dam, 1978; MS055.003.024.00031 (Box 24)
  - Draft scope of services for Mystic River hydrology study, 1976; MS055.003.024.00032 (Box 24)
  - Is the flooding of Alewife Brook a mere local phenomenon?, 1976; MS055.003.024.00033 (Box 24)
  - Traffic analysis: Alewife/North Cambridge area, 1977; MS055.003.025.00001 (Box 25)
  - Red Line extension, Harvard Square to Arlington Heights, volume 1: draft environmental impact statement, 1976; MS055.003.025.00002 (Box 25)
  - Final environmental impact statement: Red Line extension, Harvard Square to Arlington Heights, volume 2, 1977; MS055.003.025.00003 (Box 25)
  - Final environmental impact statement: Red Line extension, Harvard Square to Arlington Heights, volume 3, 1977; MS055.003.025.00004 (Box 25)
  - Arlington, Mass.: comprehensive plan summary report, 1962; MS055.003.025.00005 (Box 25)
  - Cambridgepark: draft environmental impact report, 1983; MS055.003.025.00006 (Box 25)
  - Final environmental impact report: MBTA Alewife Station interim access, 1984; MS055.003.025.00007 (Box 25)
  - Final combined sewer overflow facilities plan and final environmental impact report, 1990; MS055.003.025.00008 (Box 25)
  - Report on the Mystic River, MS055.003.025.00009 (Box 25)
  - Governing Metropolitan Boston, 1972; MS055.003.025.00010 (Box 25)
  - Boston Local Growth Policy Committee, regional and state issues, draft statement, 1976; MS055.003.025.00011 (Box 25)
  - Perspectives on growth: excerpts from local growth policy statements, 1977; MS055.003.025.00012 (Box 25)
  - Nonzoning Land-use Protection Techniques, 1978; MS055.003.025.00013 (Box 25)
  - A guide to river protection in Massachusetts, 1983; MS055.003.025.00014 (Box 25)
  - Metropolitan District Commission water supply study and environmental impact report: 2020, phase 2, 1982; MS055.003.025.00015 (Box 25)
  - River workbook, 1988; MS055.003.025.00016 (Box 25)
  - Land use study of county property, 1990; MS055.003.025.00017 (Box 25)
  - Multi-objective river corridor planning workshops, 1989; MS055.003.025.00018 (Box 25)
  - Guides for progress: development opportunities for Metropolitan Boston, 1968; MS055.003.025.00019 (Box 25)
  - Guides for progress: development opportunities for Metropolitan Boston, 1968; MS055.003.025.00020 (Box 25)
  - Wastewater facility planning guidelines: recreation and open space opportunities, 1980; MS055.003.025.00021 (Box 25)
  - Stewardship, 1965; MS055.003.025.00022 (Box 25)
  - A guide to Lexington conservation lands, 1976; MS055.003.025.00023 (Box 25)
  - The role of citizen advisory groups in water resources planning, 1976; MS055.003.025.00024 (Box 25)
  - Future land development and water quality, Mystic and Aberjona Rivers (preliminary copy), MS055.003.025.00025 (Box 25)
  - A plan to preserve and enhance the value of Horn Pond Mountain Park, 1972; MS055.003.025.00026 (Box 25)
  - Water source policy study, 1977; MS055.003.025.00027 (Box 25)
  - MRWA statement on Red Line extension, 1976; MS055.003.025.00028 (Box 25)
  - Technical memoranda: Arlington Reservoir Beach, 1980; MS055.003.025.00029 (Box 25)
  - Arlington Reservoir improvements, 1980; MS055.003.025.00030 (Box 25)
  - Bellis Circle, 1985 -- 1986; MS055.003.025.00031 (Box 25)
  - Recommended highway and transit plan, 1969; MS055.003.025.00032 (Box 25)
  - Draft executive summary, combined sewer overflow facilities plan, 1989; MS055.003.026.00001 (Box 26)
  - Draft executive summary, combined sewer overflow facilities plan, 1989; MS055.003.026.00002 (Box 26)
  - Draft combined sewer overflow facilities plan environmental impact report, volume 1, 1989; MS055.003.026.00003 (Box 26)
  - Draft combined sewer overflow facilities plan environmental impact report, volume 1, 1989; MS055.003.026.00004 (Box 26)
  - Draft combined sewer overflow facilities plan environmental impact report, volume 1, 1989; MS055.003.026.00005 (Box 26)
  - Draft combined sewer overflow facilities plan, draft environmental impact report appendices, 1989; MS055.003.026.00006 (Box 26)
  - Draft combined sewer overflow facilities plan, draft environmental impact report executive summary, 1989; MS055.003.026.00007 (Box 26)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan, technical memo 3-4: project maps, 1988; MS055.003.026.00008 (Box 26)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan, technical memo 5-1A: interim water quality impact evaluation, 1988; MS055.003.026.00009 (Box 26)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan, technical memo 7-2: update of satellite storage and treatment projects from the 1982 facilities pPlans (draft), 1988; MS055.003.026.00010 (Box 26)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities pPlan, technical memo 7-4: deep tunnel storage system performance analysis, 1988; MS055.003.026.00011 (Box 26)
  - Combined sewer overflows, 1990; MS055.003.026.00012 (Box 26)
  - Sewerage and drainage facilities, Cambridge, Mass., 1968; MS055.003.026.00013 (Box 26)
  - Final combined sewer overflow facilities plan and final environmental impact report, volume 1: executive summary, 1990; MS055.003.026.00014 (Box 26)
  - Combined sewer overflows, 1986 -- 1987; MS055.003.026.00015 (Box 26)
  - Combined sewer overflows, 1987 -- 1990; MS055.003.026.00016 (Box 26)
  - Draft of groundwater report, MS055.003.026.00017 (Box 26)
  - Glacial geology of the Mystic Lakes: Fresh Pond area, Massachusetts, 1959; MS055.003.026.00018 (Box 26)
  - Institutional aspects of wastewater management: the Boston case study, MS055.003.026.00019 (Box 26)
  - Public hearing of the Metropolitan District Commission: combined sewer overflow in the Charles River Basin study area, 1980; MS055.003.026.00020 (Box 26)
  - Analysis of urban stormwater runoff and combined sewer overflows in the Boston Metropolitan Area, 1978; MS055.003.026.00021 (Box 26)
  - Alewife correspondence, 1980 -- 1982; MS055.003.026.00022 (Box 26)
  - Traffic capacity and safety analysis of the Alewife interim access, 1985; MS055.003.026.00023 (Box 26)
  - Review comments and recommendations: the draft environmental impact statement at Alewife, 1987; MS055.003.026.00024 (Box 26)
  - Winchester, 1985; MS055.003.026.00025 (Box 26)
  - Reponsiveness survey: town of Lexington, Mass., facility plan for wastewater collection system, 1983; MS055.003.026.00026 (Box 26)
  - The Mystic River Basin: a preliminary report, 1977; MS055.003.026.00027 (Box 26)
  - Canoe guide, 1981; MS055.003.027.00001 (Box 27)
  - Eutrophication, 1978 -- 1984; MS055.003.027.00002 (Box 27)
  - Urban runoff, MS055.003.027.00003 (Box 27)
  - Water quality survey, 1981; MS055.003.027.00004 (Box 27)
  - Water quality, MS055.003.027.00005 (Box 27)
  - Draft environmental impact statement, preliminary location report, program package evaluation report, 1972; MS055.003.028.00001 (Box 28)
  - Water pollution aspects of urban runoff, 1969; MS055.003.029.00001 (Box 29)
  - Wetlands, 1965 -- 1988; MS055.003.029.00002 (Box 29)
  - Wetlands pamphlets, MS055.003.029.00003 (Box 29)
  - Criminal enforcement of the Wetlands Protection Act, 1987; MS055.003.029.00004 (Box 29)
  - Report to Woburn Commission on flood plain and wetlands zoning, 1973; MS055.003.029.00005 (Box 29)
  - Workplan for the Mystic River Watershed urban runoff project, 1979; MS055.003.029.00006 (Box 29)
  - Guide to important characteristics and values of freshwater wetlands in the Northeast, 1973; MS055.003.029.00007 (Box 29)
  - Urban runoff, 1976 -- 1982; MS055.003.029.00008 (Box 29)
  - Urban runoff pamphlets, 1976 -- 1979; MS055.003.029.00009 (Box 29)
  - Urban stormwater runoff presentation, 1977; MS055.003.029.00010 (Box 29)
  - Urban runoff correspondence, 1976 -- 1982; MS055.003.029.00011 (Box 29)
  - Soil survey of Middlesex County, Massachusetts, 1924; MS055.003.029.00012 (Box 29)
  - Geology and ground-water conditions in the Wilmington-Reading area, Massachusetts, 1964; MS055.003.029.00013 (Box 29)
- Maps, 1912 -- 1986; 1967 -- 1990; MS055.004; 0.0 Linear Feet
  This series contains maps relating to various elements of the MRWA's projects and interests.
  This series is not arranged.
  - Major thoroughfare system, Boston, 1972; MS055.004.029.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 29)
  - Zoning map, town of Arlington, 1968; MS055.004.029.00002 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 29)
  - MAPC water quality project, Mystic River Basin, conflicts between patterns and zoning, MS055.004.029.00003 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 29)
  - MAPC Mystic River quality project, Mystic River Basin, MS055.004.029.00004 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 29)
  - Alewife urban design, alternative 2, residential community urban design concept, MS055.004.029.00005 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 29)
  - Alewife urban design, alternative 2, residential emphasis illustrative isometric, MS055.004.029.00006 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 29)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts Metropolitan District Commission Combined sewer overflow project inner Harbor Basin area facilities plan, plan of existing sewerage system, MS055.004.029.00007 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 29)
  - Alewife Brook Parkway & Alewife Brook location plan (1 of 2), MS055.004.029.00008 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 29)
  - Alewife Brook Parkway & Alewife Brook location plan (2 of 2), MS055.004.029.00009 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 29)
  - Town of Arlington conservation plan, 1967; MS055.004.029.00010 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 29)
  - Combined Sewer Overflow Project plan of existing sewerage system over overflow drainage area boundaries, MS055.004.029.00011 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 29)
  - Comprehensive Plan, Arlington Planning Board, 1962; MS055.004.029.00012 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 29)
  - Return to Location Section, Room 716, Department of Public Works, MS055.004.029.00013 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 29)
  - MBTA Red Line extension, MS055.004.030.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 7, Folder 30)
  - Land use, 1978; MS055.004.030.00002 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 7, Folder 30)
  - Alewife Department of Public Works, 1974; MS055.004.030.00003 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 7, Folder 30)
  - MBTA Red Line extension notice of intent, MS055.004.031.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 7, Folder 31)
  - Plan of Land in Arlington, MA Showing Proposed corrective work to be done on Mill Brook, 1979-08; MS055.004.032.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 32)
  - Metropolitan Area Planning Committee Water Quality Program, Mystic River Basin, suitability for development, MS055.004.032.00002 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 32)
  - Metropolitan Area Planning Committee Water Quality Program, Mystic River Basin, environmental pattern, MS055.004.032.00003 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 32)
  - Combined Sewer Overflow Project, Inner Harbor Basin Area facilities plan, plan of existing sewerage system, overflow drainage area boundaries, MS055.004.032.00004 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 32)
  - Combined Sewer Overflow Project, Inner Harbor Basin area facilities plan, plan of existing sewerage system, overflow drainage area boundaries, MS055.004.032.00005 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 32)
  - Combined Sewer Overflow Project, Inner Harbor Basin area facilities plan, plan of existing sewerage system, overflow drainage area boundaries, MS055.004.032.00006 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 32)
  - Off-street parking, 1973; MS055.004.032.00007 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 32)
  - Mill Brook stream path analysis, MS055.004.032.00008 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 32)
  - Alewife Reservation, 1977-11; MS055.004.032.00009 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 32)
  - Field Investigation of Uncontrolled Hazardous Waste Sites, Woburn, MA Groundwater Study. sheet 1 of 4, 1981-03-10; MS055.004.032.00010 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 32)
  - Field Investigation of Uncontrolled Hazardous Waste Sites. Woburn, MA Sheet 2 of 4, 1981-03-10; MS055.004.032.00011 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 32)
  - Field Investigation of Uncontrolled Hazardous Waste Sites. Woburn, MA Sheet 3 of 4, 1981-03-10; MS055.004.032.00012 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 32)
  - Field Investigation of Uncontrolled Hazardous Waste Sites. Woburn, MA Sheet, 1981-03-10; MS055.004.032.00013 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 32)
  - Distribution of selenium, 1983; MS055.004.033.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 33)
  - Distribution of silver, 1983; MS055.004.033.00002 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 33)
  - Contour map of arsenic and lead concentrations, 1983; MS055.004.033.00003 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 33)
  - Contour Map of Chromium concentrations, 1983; MS055.004.033.00004 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 33)
  - Contour map of copper and zinc concentration, 1983; MS055.004.033.00005 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 33)
  - Location of hide residue areas, 1983; MS055.004.033.00006 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 33)
  - Distribution of organics, 1983; MS055.004.033.00007 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 33)
  - Distribution of Thallium, 1983; MS055.004.033.00008 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 33)
  - Harvard Square to Alewife Brook, Preliminary site plan, Alewife Brook Station, 1967; MS055.004.034.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 34)
  - Firm flood insurance rate map, Town of Arlington, Revised Preliminary, MS055.004.034.00002 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 34)
    Panels 1 and 2. No Date Available
  - Firm flood insurance rate map, Town of Arlington, Revised Preliminary, MS055.004.034.00003 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 34)
    Panel 2. No Date Available
  - Firm flood insurance rate map, Town of Arlington, Map Index, Revised Preliminary, MS055.004.034.00004 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 34)
  - Floodway flood boundary and floodway map, Town of Arlington, Massachusetts, Middlesex County, Revised Preliminary, MS055.004.034.00005 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 34)
  - Floodway flood boundary and floodway map, Town of Arlington, Massachusetts, Middlesex County, Map Index Revised Preliminary, MS055.004.034.00006 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 34)
  - Recommended 208 areawide plan, 1977; MS055.004.034.00007 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 34)
  - Harvard Square to Alewife Brook, Preliminary site plan, Alewife Brook Station, 1967-11-06; MS055.004.034.00008 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 34)
  - Combined Sewer Overflow Project Inner Harbor Basin Area Facilities Plan: 1978 and 1979 surf and river sampling sites, MS055.004.034.00009 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 34)
  - Mill Brook Valley interceptor sewer facility plan, existing interceptor sewer system draft, 1979; MS055.004.035.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 35)
  - Notes: A Joint Winchester-Woburn study, MS055.004.035.00002 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 35)
  - Mill Brook Valley relief sewer, MS055.004.035.00003 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 35)
  - Drawdown of the water table after 30 days of pumpage from Wells G and H, 1986-01-03; MS055.004.035.00004 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 35)
  - Drawdown of water-level in the wells completed in deep stratified drift and bedrock after 30 days of pumpage from Wells G and H, 1986-01-03; MS055.004.035.00005 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 35)
  - Altitude of water-table in the vicinity of Wells G and H, 1985; MS055.004.035.00006 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 35)
  - Altitude of the water-table after 30 days of pumpage from Wells G and H, 1986-01-03; MS055.004.035.00007 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 35)
  - Altitude of the potentiometric surface of wells completed in deep stratified drift and bedrock after 30 days of pumpage from Wells G and H, 1986-01-03; MS055.004.035.00008 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 35)
  - Industriplex 128, Woburn, Mass., 1978; MS055.004.035.00009 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 35)
    Revised 1979.
  - Alewife urban design, 1977; MS055.004.035.00010 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 35)
  - Altitude of the potentiometric surface of wells completed in deep stratified drift and bedrock in the vicinity of wells G and H, 1912 -- 1985; MS055.004.035.00011 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 35)
  - Interstate 93-Rt.16, Medford, Mass., study corridor, 1974; MS055.004.036.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 36)
  - Preliminary design report, Harvard Square-Alewife Brook extension, 1967; MS055.004.036.00002 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 36)
  - Area of investigation, 1983; MS055.004.036.00003 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 36)
  - Conductivity measuring point location map, 1983; MS055.004.036.00004 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 36)
  - Locations of test borings and pits, 1983; MS055.004.036.00005 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 36)
  - Initial interpretation of conductivity results, 1983; MS055.004.036.00006 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 36)
  - Reinterpretation of conductivity results, 1983; MS055.004.036.00007 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 36)
  - Distribution of lead, 1983; MS055.004.036.00008 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 36)
  - Distribution of arsenic, 1983; MS055.004.036.00009 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 36)
  - Distribution of chromium, 1983; MS055.004.036.00010 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 36)
  - Distribution of barium, 1983; MS055.004.036.00011 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 36)
  - Distribution of cadmium, 1983; MS055.004.036.00012 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 36)
  - Distribution of copper, 1983; MS055.004.036.00013 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 36)
  - Distribution of mercury, 1983; MS055.004.036.00014 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 36)
  - Distribution of antimony, 1983; MS055.004.036.00015 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 36)
  - Distribution of nickel, 1983; MS055.004.036.00016 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 36)
  - Distribution of Zinc, 1983-02; MS055.004.036.00017 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 6, Folder 36)
  - Interstate 93/Rt. 16 year 2000 forecast, alternative 1, 1974; MS055.004.037.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 37)
  - Interstate 93/Rt. 16 year 2000 forecast, alternative 2, 1974; MS055.004.037.00002 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 37)
  - Interstate 93/Rt. 16 year 2000 forecast, alternative 1, 1976; MS055.004.037.00003 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 37)
  - Interstate 93/Rt. 16 year 2000 forecast, alternative 2, 1976; MS055.004.037.00004 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 37)
  - Interstate 93/Rt. 16 year 2000 forecast, alternative 3, 1976; MS055.004.037.00005 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 37)
  - Interstate 93/Rt. 16 year 2000 forecast, no build, 1976; MS055.004.037.00006 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 37)
  - Great Meadows proposed science park, MS055.004.038.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 38)
  - Metropolitan Area Planning Committee Water Quality Project, Mystic River Basin, general soils, MS055.004.038.00002 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 38)
    Date Not Available
  - Wellington Station area environmental assessment, MS055.004.038.00003 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 38)
  - Aerial photo, MS055.004.038.00004 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 38)
  - Wetlands protection district zoning map No. W-7, 1973-03-19; MS055.004.038.00005 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 38)
  - Wetlands protection district zoning map No. W-8, 1973-03-19; MS055.004.038.00006 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 38)
  - Wetlands protection district zoning map No. W-12, 1973-03-19; MS055.004.038.00007 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 38)
  - Wetlands protection district zoning map No. W-13, 1973-03-19; MS055.004.038.00008 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9, Folder 38)
- MRWA correspondence, 1964 -- 1997; 1967 -- 1990; MS055.005; 0.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains correspondence between members of the MRWA and outside agencies and individuals relating to various projects and concerns of the organization.
  - Correspondence, 1964 -- 1969; MS055.005.038.00001 (Box 38)
  - Correspondence, 1970 -- 1975; MS055.005.038.00002 (Box 38)
  - Correspondence, 1976 -- 1977; MS055.005.038.00003 (Box 38)
  - Correspondence, 1978 -- 1979; MS055.005.038.00004 (Box 38)
  - Correspondence, 1980 -- 1983; MS055.005.038.00005 (Box 38)
  - Correspondence, 1984 -- 1987; MS055.005.038.00006 (Box 38)
  - Correspondence, 1988 -- 1990; MS055.005.038.00007 (Box 38)
  - Correspondence, 1990 -- 1997; MS055.005.038.00008 (Box 38)
  - Correspondence, MS055.005.038.00009 (Box 38)
- MRWA office files, 1966 -- 1995; 1974 -- 1980; MS055.006; 1.0 Linear Feet
  This series contains the office files of the Mystic River Watershed Association. These files include various committee minutes, by-laws, and other official organizational documents.
  - MRWA projects for the year 1981, 1980; MS055.006.039.00001 (Box 39)
  - Fiore lawsuit, 1971 -- 1975; MS055.006.039.00002 (Box 39)
  - MRWA charter and bylaws, 1971 -- 1975; MS055.006.039.00003 (Box 39)
  - Non-MRWA notices, memos, and minutes, 1973 -- 1988; MS055.006.039.00004 (Box 39)
  - Internal communications, 1977 -- 1989; MS055.006.039.00005 (Box 39)
  - Meeting agendas, 1978 -- 1987; MS055.006.039.00006 (Box 39)
  - MRWA correspondence, 1971 -- 1986; MS055.006.039.00007 (Box 39)
  - Dr. Meyer's comments: correspondence, 1975 -- 1987; MS055.006.039.00008 (Box 39)
  - Dr. Meyer's comments: Alewife Task Force, 1975 -- 1976; MS055.006.039.00009 (Box 39)
  - Dr. Herbert Meyer, 1974 -- 1990; MS055.006.039.00010 (Box 39)
  - MRWA history, 1966 -- 1988; MS055.006.039.00011 (Box 39)
  - Minutes, 1970 -- 1986; MS055.006.040.00001 (Box 40)
  - Minutes, 1987 -- 1988; MS055.006.040.00002 (Box 40)
  - Media coverage, 1976 -- 1979; MS055.006.040.00003 (Box 40)
  - Minutes, 1991 -- 1995; MS055.006.040.00004 (Box 40)
- MRWA culture, 1976 -- 1988; 1976 -- 1987; MS055.007; 0.25 Linear Feet